Hold on.
I'm going to say so.
You've got to be a genius to think to lose that much weight.
It's very warm in here.
From the color to the temperature.
And I'm really excited.
We're going to do an episode called
Side Effects of Being...
Light skin.
And I know y'all are already like,
What?
We're going to do another one after we can't say how sad we'll be.
You know we're going to have an intellectual conversation.
You are in the basses.
Okay.
Side Effects of Being Light Skin
with DeWanna Dixon of Don't Call Me White Girl.
Now available wherever you get your podcasts.
And you can watch the premiere tomorrow
on YouTube at AmandaSealsTV,
4 p.m. Pacific, 7 p.m. Eastern.